-嗨！ -嗨！
- Hey,guys. - Hey.
- Hi. - Hey.
啊，有点事和你们谈谈。
We need to talk about something.
我们觉得... 今年我们不能再做感恩节晚餐了。
Yeah. We don't feel like we can host Thanksgiving this year.
-什么，什么？ -什么，你是在开玩笑吧
- What? - Are you kidding?
嗯，由于工作，还有领养孩子的压力
Well,it's just with work and the stress of adoption..
我们只是觉得没有精力弄了。
we don't feel like we have the energy.
而且，每年都让我们受累，不公平。
Plus,we don't think it's fair that every year the burden falls on us.
这不像你啊！
That doesn't sound like you.
这像是莫尼卡的话！
That's Monica talking.
-不，不，这是我们两个人的决定！ -这一定是她把话语放进了你的嘴里
- No,we made this decision together. - She's putting words in your mouth.
你不应该把话送到我们口中 而是把火鸡送到我们口中……
Don't you put words in people's mouths. You put turkey in people's mouths.
无法相信 这可是艾玛的第一个感恩节！
I can't believe this. This is Emma's first Thanksgiving.
-不是... -不是？她什么时候出生的？
- No,it's not. - It's not? When was she born?
我个人认为，你们是应该休息一下子了。
Well,personally,I think it's great you're giving yourself a break.
-谢谢，菲比。 -不客气,这样很好
- Thank you,Phoebe. - Sure. It's just as well.
还有，去年的晚餐棒极了 今年她不可能做得更好了。
I mean,last year wasn't very good. I think she's losing her touch.
-什么？你搞错了，女士！ -是么？
- What? You are way off,lady. - Am I? Really? Am I?
那你就再弄一次，证明我错。
Well,why don't you cook Thanksgiving dinner and prove me wrong.
你想想 你是在试图超过去年的顶峰
Well,think about it. You'd be trying to top what you did last year.
你是在和...自己竞争！
You'd be in competition with yourself.
真对我胃口！
That's my favorite kind.
好吧，今年，我们继续！
Okay,we are doing this.
别让自己这么容易被左右。
Don't let yourself get manipulated this way.
不关你的事，钱德 这是我和……“我”之间的事情！
Stay out of this,Chandler. This is between me and me.
我们应该一起决定啊！
We are supposed to make these decisions together.
还记得费尔医生对你说的话么？
Did you not watch the Dr. Phil I taped for you?
迟到的感恩节
The.One.With.The.Late.Thanksgiving
-嗨 -嗨，感恩节快乐！
- Hey. - Hi. Happy Thanksgiving.
是的，火鸡殉难日快乐！
Happy Meatless Turkey-Murder Day.
我从布里克面包房订了些巧克力派
You guys,I ordered some chocolate pies from that bakery on Bleeker.
-你们能帮我去取过来么？ -你不自己作派吗？
- Could you pick them up for me? - You're not making the pies?
不，我不做巧克力派的。
I don't make chocolate pies.
我小时候参加过一个吃派比赛
When I was younger,I entered this pie-eating contest.
吃的太多了，导致我一想就恶心。
I ate so many that the thought of them makes me sick.
那你赢了没有？
Did you at least win the contest?
两分钟吃了12个外加一罐！
Two minutes,twelve pies and a part of one tin.
-好吧，我们4点见。 -很让人期待哦！
- Okay,I'll see you guys at 4. - Can't wait.
去年的莫妮卡,我要你好看！
This dinner is gonna be so great. In your face,last-year me.
-嗨，瑞秋 - 嗯？
- Hey,Rach? - Yeah.
艾玛今天有事么？
What's Emma doing today?
嗯，她啊，我只知道她今天要和律师见面
Well,let's see,I know that she has a meeting with her lawyer..
然后要去大便
and then she has to make a very big poop.
-怎么了？ -嗯，我想让她参加婴儿选美。
- Why? - I want to enter her in a baby pageant.
哦，天哪，这是我听说过的最奇怪的事情。
Oh,my God. That's the creepiest thing I've ever heard.
我朋友苏珊带她的孩子参加了
Okay,but before you say no,my friend Suzanne is entering her kid.
和艾玛比起来，那小家伙就像只小狗！
And compared to Emma,she's a real dog.
-哦，菲比，所有孩子都是美丽的！ -好吧
- Phoebe,all babies are beautiful. - Oh,okay.
菲比，难道我们只是为了一个奖杯
No. Phoebe,just the idea of pitting one baby against another..
就把孩子们比来比去，决定谁更漂亮么？
I mean,you know,and judging who's cuter just for a trophy..
- 一千美金。 -对此我很感兴趣！
- And a thousand dollars. - is something I'm very interested in.
对了，别告诉罗斯。
Oh,please,do not tell Ross.
他始终不信任那些内部的...
He still believes that what's on the inside is important.
对了，艾玛得穿牛仔装！
Okay. And Emma needs a cowgirl outfit for the competition.
感恩节我上哪儿找牛仔装啊？
Where am I gonna get a cowgirl outfit on Thanksgiving?
让我想想……
Well,I was thinking..
把乔伊的菜地娃的衣服扒了！
Take the clothes off Joey's Cabbage Patch Kid!
又有人把指挥棒给掉了？
Did someone drop the baton again?
为什么每次都是堪萨斯的？
Why come all the way from Kansas to do that?
我不是越来越老，而是越来越好！
I don't get older,I just get better.
你知道我刚想到什么？
You know what just occurred to me?
这可能是最后一次 只有我们两个人一起过感恩节了。
This could be our last Thanksgiving just the two of us.
我觉得，我们很快就会有个孩子了！
I mean,we could be getting a baby soon.
-你怎么知道？ -有人会选择我们的。
- You don't know that. - Somebody's gonna pick us.
可是这几周我们都没收到领养消息！
But we haven't heard a thing from the adoption agency.
我敢保证
I'm telling you,it's gonna happen.
明年会是你、我、还有海明威・宾！
Next year,it's gonna be you,me and little Hemingway Bing.
- 怎么了？他可是我最喜欢的作家。 -说出他一本书的名字。
- What? He's my favorite author. - Name one of his books.
《糖衣陷阱》？（作者：约翰・格林斯海姆）
The Firm?
好吧，火鸡已经在烤箱里了 添料也准备好了。
Okay,let's see. Okay,the turkey's in the oven. The stuffing is ready.
你知道么，你总是自己弄这些东西 今年让我帮帮你吧。
You know,you always cook this meal all by yourself. Let me help this year.
哦，钱德，这太好了！
Oh,Chandler,that's sweet.
但你不用一直按费尔医生说的做
But you don't have to do everything Dr. Phil tells you to do.
我是认真的。让我做点什么吧 不是火鸡，也不是填馅，做点不难的东西。
I'm serious,let me do something. Just not the turkey. Nothing high-profile.
我想想……啊，酸梅酱！
Okay,let's see. Oh,the cranberry sauce.
容易做，而且大家也不是很在意那东西！
It's easy to make,and no one really cares about it.
说来听听？
Tell me more.
我去对门儿检查别的 你先把这个洗干净吧。
I'm gonna go check on something across the hall. You start by washing these.
别用洗涤剂！！
Not with soap!
你肯定没吃过我做的烤土豆……
You obviously haven't tasted my Palmolive potatoes.
-嘿，猜猜乔伊拿到了什么？ -三张今天纽约游骑兵的票（美国冰球大联盟NHL）！
- Hi. Hey,guess what Joey has. - Three tickets to today's Rangers game!
兄弟，我是让他猜的！
Dude,I wanted him to guess.
-哦，天哪！ -是啊，而且是好座位哦！
- Oh,my God. - Yeah,they're great seats too.
-猜猜什么位置？ -正中间！
- Guess where they are. - Center ice.
我是不是和你有什么过节？
Did I do something to you?
-嗯，比赛一点开始。 -怎样？
- The game's at 1. - So?
-晚饭4点开始，我们赶不回来的。 -那我们就提前退场，这样时间就够了。
- Dinner's at 4. We'll never make it back. - So we'll leave before it's over.
你现在这么说，可是到时候必定要花很多时间回来的
But it could take us a long time to get back home.
另外 乔伊可能会迷路，还得把他领回来。
Plus,Joey could get lost and they could have to page us to go pick him up.
老兄，才发生过两次而已！
Dude,two times that happened!
莫尼卡为了做晚饭忙了一整天
Look,Monica's been working hard all day.
她希望她的晚餐最重要，我们不该去的。
She didn't want to host in the first place. We shouldn't go.
他说得没错儿
He's right,man.
-好吧。那么四点钟见。 -嗯
- Yeah,I guess. So we'll see you at 4. - Okay.
准备好品尝我的特制酸梅酱哦！
And get ready to taste my very special cranberries.
或者，应该叫做“钱梅”...
Or should I say "Chan-berries"?
伙计，又不是在演轻喜剧
That's some gentle comedy,dude.
-我们要去看比赛吧？ -是的！
- We're still going to the game,right? - Yeah.
-嘿！ -菲比，我想走了
- Hey. - Phoebe,listen,I think we gotta go.
这地方让我坐立不安。
This place is freaking me out.
你看到那边那个人了么 我可不认为他带来的是个孩子！
I've been watching this guy over there. I don't think he came with a kid.
但你现在不能离开啊
But we can't leave now.
最被看好的那个孩子海利
There was this one baby,Haley,who was favored to win..
因为感冒不能来
she got croup,so she had to stay home.
竞争才刚刚开始哦！
This competition just blew wide-open,folks.
菲比，这太奇怪了
Phoebe,it's just too weird.
我看见一个一岁的小孩穿连裤袜！
I just saw a 1-year-old with pantyhose on.
哦，我就觉得我们准备不够充分
Oh,I know. We should've been more prepared.
我觉得，咱们最有力的竞争对手是卡米隆。
It's okay. Now,the way I see it,our real competition now is Cameron.
哦，天哪，她的衣服被脱掉了
My God,they just took her sweater off.
看她的手臂，就像...米其林 （著名轮胎的卡通形象，绿色的）
Look at those arms. Hello,Michelin Man.
菲比，已经三点钟了 而他们还没有评审到艾玛这一组
Phoebe,come on. You know what,it's already 3:00.
我们该走了，回去吃饭。
They haven't even gotten to Emma's group yet. We got dinner.
但艾玛今天肯定能赢
But Emma's got what it takes. She could go all the way!
-菲比，冷静点。 -好吧，
- Phoebe,you have to calm down. - Okay.
瑞秋，现在 这附近最漂亮的宝贝们都在这里了。
Rachel,the hottest babies in the tri-state area are in this room right now.
而我听见一个评审说 没人比得过艾玛。
I overheard a judge say that not one of them holds a candle to Emma.
-真的？ -没错！
- Really? - Yeah.
-你听见他们这么说？ -对。
- You heard him say that? - Yeah.
好吧，那就让我们 给其他的孩子们一点悲惨的回忆！
All right. Okay. All right,let's give these babies something to cry about.
太好了，开工吧！艾玛需要化妆。
Good. Let's get down to business. Emma needs some makeup.
什么？
What?
她应该比其他孩子看起来更漂亮！
She's gonna look washed-out next to the others.
菲比，我不会让你给我的孩子化妆的！
No,I'm not letting you put makeup on my baby.
-为什么不？ -因为我已经给她化过了！
- Why not? - Because I already did.
鲍伯，干掉那家伙！
You suck! Get off the ice,you idiot!
-太精彩了！ -没错，耶！
- What a game. - I know. Yeah.
-真遗憾钱德错过了这场比赛！ -我也替他觉得遗憾
- I can't believe Chandler's missing this. - I'm sorry he's not here.
但我要说的是，我真的很喜欢这个“玉米片”座！
But I gotta say,I am really enjoying nacho chair.
嗯，要是你不总是把我的手打开， 我可能也会吃不少呢
Yeah,I'd probably enjoy it more if you didn't keep batting my hand away.
-哦！ -这位置太棒了！
- Yeah! - These seats are great.
是啊，没错！ 上次假期我在这看滑冰比赛，座位太远了
I know,I know. When I was here for "Holidays on lce"..
关颖珊（花样滑冰世界冠军）根本就看不到我举的条幅。
I was sitting so far away,Michelle Kwan couldn't read my banner.
老兄,我认为她知道你心里有她
Dude,I'm sure she knows you heart her.
希望吧
I hope so.
嘿，我们该走了啦，回去吃饭。
We'd better get going. If we don't leave now,we're gonna be late.
可比赛太精彩了！ 我们可以晚回去点吧，女生们应该准时的
But it's a tie game. So we're a little late. The girls will be there.
再进一个球再走啦
Let's just stay for one more goal.
-不好吧.. -再进攻一轮？
- I don't know. - One more fight.
-好吧。 -好吧。
- Okay. - Okay.
大家都哪里去了？他们迟到了45分钟！
Where is everybody? They're 45 minutes late.
我不相信他们会不来！我辛苦了一天 而我这么辛苦是为了什么？
I can't believe they're not here. I slave and I slave for what?
他们毁了我的酸梅日！
They've ruined Cranberry Day.
-我们迟到了多久？ -45分钟
- How late are we? - Forty-five minutes.
- 给. - 好的.
- Here. - Okay.
瑞秋和菲比应该已经到了 也就是说她们应该已经开始了
Rachel and Phoebe are already there,so they probably started without us.
让我们溜进去，这样谁都不会注意我们的。
We could just slip in,and no one needs to know where we were.
-你不把这个泡沫大手指扔掉吗？ - 哦，才不呢！
- You may want to lose the foam finger. - Oh,no,no,no.
我知道你想抢走它！
You just want to put it on your hand.
-你们没在里面？ -不，我们迟到了！
- You're not at Thanksgiving? - No,we're late.
-你们在这里干什么？ -我们也迟到了！
- What are you doing here? - We're late too.
我们本以为你们不会迟到的！
We figured we could be late because you'd be on time.
别用这个指着我，崔比亚尼！
Don't point that thing at me,Tribbiani.
-那...里面没人，莫尼卡会杀了我们的！ -你们到什么地方去了？
- Nobody's here? Monica's gonna kill us. - Yeah,where were you?
- 啊… -那是什么奖杯？
- Well.. - Yeah,what's with the trophy?
嗯，我们去参加拼字大赛了。
Well,we were at a spelling bee.
我赢了！
And I won.
你在感恩节这天 赢得了一场成人拼字游戏？
You won an adult Thanksgiving Day spelling bee?
是的,Y-E-S，是的！
Yes. Y-E-S. Yes.
让我看看…… 超级小可爱，纽约区。
Let me see this. "Grand Supreme Little Darling,New York Division"?
那便是我！
That's me.
你们让艾玛参加了选美比赛？
You entered Emma in a beauty pageant?
而且还给她化了妆？
And it looks like she put makeup on her.
等等，等等 我好像在什么地方见过这身牛仔...
Wait a second. Where have I seen that cowgirl outfit before?
无法置信，她是我们的女儿！
I can't believe this. She's our daughter.
你把她当成观赏狗一样，不可饶恕
That you would treat her like some kind of show dog is inexcusable.
-她为我们赢得了一千美元！ -啊，是一年一次的吗……
- She won a thousand dollars. - So this is an annual thing?
啊，这是爱丽舍・梅・艾莫瑞的装备！
That's Alicia May Emory's outfit!
伙计们，有人在里面要发火了！
Guys,there are people in there who are not getting any happier.
-天哪，我们该怎么办？ -我不知道，你们想吧,我先把艾玛送回去。
- What are we gonna do? - I gotta put Emma down for a nap.
哦，瑞秋，至少给个主意嘛
And,Rach,while you're in there,throw something on Alicia May.
-我们该怎么说？ -我们可以说，我们被抢劫了
- All right,what are we gonna say? - We'll say that we were mugged.
当有人被抢了的时候，是不能生气的！
You can't get mad at someone who's been mugged.
嗯，不错，但你看起来不像被抢过。
Good. But you don't look like you were mugged.
不像..这样才像
No. Here.
嘿！
Hey!
你有没有听到什么？
Do you hear something?
-他们都在外面！ -让我看看！
- They're out there. - Let me see.
我真没办法相信，他们迟到了一小时 还在那里聊天！
I can't believe this. They're an hour late,and they're just standing there talking.
一切都乱套了，乔伊有只大手！
Everything's so distorted. It looks like Joey has a giant hand.
上面写“游骑兵”，他们去看比赛了！
That says "Rangers" on it. They went to the game.
哦，这太可怕了！
Oh,they are in for a world of pain.
-罗斯的衬衫撕坏了。 -他们不但迟到，而且衣衫不整！
- Ross' shirt is torn. - They're late and they're sloppy.
好了，艾玛睡下了。你的衬衫怎么了？
All right,Emma's napping. What happened to your shirt?
我被抢了，他们还偷走了我的钱包。
I got mugged,and they stole my pocket.
瑞秋，我们是在找借口。
We're just trying to figure out an excuse.
好吧，想想
How about this?
我们可以说，莫尼卡告诉我们是5点 而不是4点，所以我们没迟到，我们是准时的！
We could say that Monica told us 5:00,not 4:00. That way we're right on time.
或者,我们可以在房间里放些迷药，布个局！
Or we could plant PCP in the apartment and call the cops on her.
嗯，这的确是个下迷药的好办法。
That would be a good way to get rid of all the PCP we have lying around.
你可以说她说的是5点
We'll just say that she said it was 5:00.
做得自然些 所以我们根本没有迟到！
We'll just act casual. We're not late,we're right on time.
“我们知道你们在外面。”
"We know you're out there."
你觉得这是谁写的？
Who do you think it's from?
哦，太糟了，太糟了。
Oh,God,this is bad. This is so bad.
好吧，让我们进去面对他们吧。
Well,let's just go in there and face them.
我不要先进去 莫尼卡生气的面孔会让我发疯的。
I'm not going in first. I bet that vein on Monica's forehead is popping like crazy.
嗯，我也不要 那张脸就像扭曲的闪电一样……
I hate that thing. It's like a bolt of lightning.
嘿，我有主意了 我们可以玩石头剪子布，输了的先进去！
Why don't we play Rock,Paper,Scissors,and whoever loses,goes in first.
-好吧，开始吧。 -准备好了么？
- All right,I'm in. - Ready.
啊，我赢了！
I win.
-这是什么？ -火焰，赢过一切！
- What is that? - That's fire. It beats everything.
真的么？能赢过一个水球么？
Oh,really? Does it beat water balloon?
好极了，菲比，玩得真好。
Well-played,Phoebe Buffay. Well-played.
好啦好啦，让我们一起进去算了。
All right,let's all go in at the same time.
-好。 -好。
- Okay. - Okay.
-锁住了！ -哈，他们把门锁上了
- It's locked. - What? Oh,sure,now they lock it.
等他们在躺椅上 准备做爱的时候，他们就会说
When they're having sex on the couch,it's like:
“啊，快进来，快进来，我等不了了！”
"Come on in,my butt is surprisingly hairy!"
好吧。伙计们，你们怎么样啊？ 很抱歉我们迟到了
All right,come on. All right,you guys,we're so sorry we're late.
让我们进去一起吃晚餐吧！
Please let us in so we can have dinner together.
不，东西都凉了 火鸡干了，馅也松了！
No,everything's cold. The turkey's dried out and the stuffing's all soggy.
嗯，而且那碗酸梅酱也……
Yeah,and there's a bowl of cranberry sauce that's..
酸梅酱怎么了？
What happens to cranberry sauce?
-没事儿，很好。 -哦，谢天谢地。
- Nothing,it's fine. - Oh,thank God.
好啦，伙计们 真的抱歉，我们的车坏了。
Come on,you guys,we're sorry. Our subway broke down.
说谎！你们去看比赛了 我能看到乔伊的手！
That's a lie! You went to the game. I can see Joey's hand.
我说过了让你把它扔掉了！
For the love of God,take it off!
伙计们，我们是否迟到了并不重要 重要的是我们都到了
Guys,it doesn't matter why we're late. We're all here now.
让我们进去吃美味的火鸡吧！
Please let us in so we can have some of your delicious turkey.
我曾经梦到有这样的一个传真机
I had a dream once about a fax machine that did that.
这就是你们该得的火鸡！
That's all the turkey you're gonna get.
-怎么决定谁吃？ -水球！
- How are we gonna decide who gets this? - Water balloon!
我们该怎么办啊，我饿死了！
What are we gonna do? I'm starving.
哦，对了，我想起来了
I just remembered,we do have something to eat.
今天早晨莫尼卡放了点东西在烤箱里面！
Monica put something in our oven this morning.
嘿，动了它你会后悔的！
You touch that,and you will be sorry!
大伙,最好听她的 她的血管涨到前所未有的大
Guys,I'd listen to her. The vein is bigger than I've ever seen it!
天哪，是甘蓝菜！
Oh,my God,it's Brussels sprouts!
这是什么嘛，不能吃的！
That's worse than no food.
啊哈，你们喜欢莫尼卡的发臭甘蓝菜么？
All you got was Monica's stinky Brussels sprouts.
发臭的？
Stinky?
请让我呆在这一边……
Please let me stay on this side of the door.
对了，我还有以前的钥匙呢。
Oh,I know! I still have my old key.
我们可以直接把门打开！
We can just unlock the door.
我不觉得这是个好主意 他们明显不想和我们在一起。
I don't know if that's a good idea. They don't wanna be with us.
你知道吗，我也不想和他们一起
I don't wanna be with them either..
但今天是感恩节，不想在一起也要在一起！
but it's Thanksgiving,and we should not want to be together together.
让我们进去面对面的道歉吧
If I could just get in there,make a face-to-face apology..
看到我的眼睛，他们就会原谅我的。
look them in the eye,I could get them to forgive us.
-我不知道。 -我来告诉你……
- I don't know. - I'm telling you..
我做得到。
I can do it.
嗯，你做得到。
Yeah,he can do it.
啊，太美了！
It all looks so beautiful.
-那火鸡，那填料…… -那酸梅呢？
- The turkey,the stuffing. - The cranberries.
够了，猴子都会做！
Enough! A monkey could've made them.
嘿，听我说，我们真得很抱歉……
Hey,listen,guys,we feel really terrible.
他又来那什么“目光接触”了
He's doing that weird eye-contact thing.
别看他，别看他。
Don't look at him. Don't look at him.
听我说，伙计们，我们想让你们了解 我们真的，真的很抱歉……
Come on,you guys. We want you to know we're very,very sorry.
对吧，伙计们？
Right,guys?
-真的很抱歉 -非常，对不起……
- I feel terrible. - Oh,so sorry.
别让我们毁了这一天，你们如此的辛劳！
But let's not ruin this day. You've worked so hard.
让我们忘了这件事，一起吃饭吧！
Let's move past this and try to have a nice meal all together,huh?
那些漂浮着的脑袋好像说的没错。
The floating heads do make a good point.
是啊，他们真的好像很抱歉。
Yeah,they do seem to feel pretty bad.
-很抱歉 -很抱歉
- So bad. - So bad.
好吧
Okay.
好吧，你们两个去拿甜品来 我让你们进来。
Okay,you two go get the dessert,and I'll let you in.
甜品？
Dessert?
是啊，我让你和菲比去取派 你记得的，对吧？
Yeah,I asked you and Phoebe to pick up the pies. You did remember,right?
派？啊，我们以为是“奖”！ (发音相近）
Pies. Oh,we thought you said "prize."
这个！
Here.
-超级小可爱？ -恭喜！
- "Grand Supreme Little Darling"? - Congratulations!
天哪，你忘了拿派？无法置信！
Oh,my God,you forgot the pies? Well,I cannot believe this.
你们强迫我做饭，又迟到一小时
You forced me to make dinner,you're an hour late..
居然还忘记了我拜托你们做的一点点小事！
and you forget the one little thing that I asked you to do.
真的，女孩们，一点都不好
Really,girls,not cool.
好吧，你们男人又好到哪里去？ 你们说谎，去看比赛
Well,you man-heads aren't any better. You lied about going to the game.
明知道会迟到，还坚持要去。
You knew it'd make you late,and you went anyway.
我有点烦了。我们都道歉了
Hey,I'm getting a little tired of this. We said we're sorry.
今天是感恩节，是原谅之日！
It's Thanksgiving,for Pete's sakes! A day of forgiveness.
-是感谢之日吧…… -别和我唱反调！
- It's a day to be thankful. - Don't make me come up there!
现在道歉太晚了！
It's too late for apologies.
好吧，我们走，我们可以不在这里吃饭！
Fine,let's just go. I don't need your stupid dinner.
如果你们开玩笑的话，可能更可信点。
That would be a lot more convincing if you weren't drooling.
-哦，我们现在就不是么？ -对不起
- Oh,is that what that is? - Sorry.
伙计们，我们自己准备感恩节晚餐吧！
Come on,you guys,let's just do our own Thanksgiving.
-好，我做饭！ -好，走吧！
- Yeah,I'll cook. - Yeah,let's go out.
你们三个，感恩节快乐！
Yeah,you three have a nice Thanksgiving.
-三个？ -你，钱德，还有“白忙活”！
- The three of us? - Yeah. You,Chan and the vein.
-啊，我被卡住了！ -乔伊，少来！
- I'm stuck. - Joey,that is not gonna work.
不，我是认真的
No,seriously.
-我真的被卡住了 -我把你拖过来
- I'm really wedged in here. - I'll pull you through.
好。
Okay.
啊，住手，住手 我担心会弄伤我的头！
Stop,stop,I'm worried about damaging my head.
已经晚了
It's a little late for that.
快点，帮帮忙啊！
Hurry up,you gotta do something.
这不会改变什么的！
All right,well,this does not change anything.
我们需要点能增大空隙的工具。
We need to get something to grease his face.
-我们有火鸡汁！ -拿来。
- We got turkey grease. - Bring it.
我很抱歉，我把“白忙活”算作一个人
I just want to say that I'm sorry I referred to the vein as a separate person.
来了。
Here you go.
啊，味道不错
Oh,that smells good.
-好了吗？ -好，试试看。
- Okay? - Okay,try it.
没用！
It isn't working.
-把链条卸下来吧。 -快点，我都感觉不到我的耳朵了！
- We're gonna have to unscrew the chain. - Hurry,I can't feel my ears.
你曾经感觉到过耳朵么？
Can you ever feel your ears?
嗯，很有趣。
Interesting.
-钱德，你的工具哪里去了？ -啊，我把它们放在推土机里了
- Chandler,where are your tools? - Oh,I left them on my bulldozer.
我没有工具。
I don't have tools.
-我有，但被瑞秋借去了。 -我借给了罗斯。
- Well,I do,but Rachel borrowed them. - I lent them to Ross.
-我给了乔伊。 -我留在停车场了。
- I gave them to Joey. - I left them at the park.
这还真麻烦。
I'm finding it really hard not to mess with him.
我把甘蓝塞到他的裤子里
I stuffed Brussels sprouts down his pants.
很好。
Nice.
好，我去接电话
Okay,I have to get that.
当我回来的时候 我希望你和你的朋友们已经离开了。
Now,when I get back,I want you and your friends to be gone.
感恩节完了！这是“白忙活”说的！
Thanksgiving is over. The vein has spoken.
-我的头真的被卡住了！ -好吧，我会拉门
- It's really starting to hurt. - Look,I'm gonna pull on the door..
然后你们努力推 这样他就有足够的空隙出来了，好吧？
and you guys push. Maybe we can get enough room to wiggle him out,okay?
好，推吧！
Okay,so push.
啊，等下，我们正忙着……
Just a sec. We're kind of in the middle of something here.
别往我的裤子里面放东西！
Hey,stop putting things down my pants.
-来吧，伙计们，推吧！ -来，推，推，推！
- Come on,guys,push! - Yeah,come on,push!
推，推！
Push! Push!
-我的酸梅！ -我全身都是！
- My cranberries! - Man,I got food all over me.
难以置信，莫尼卡会杀了你的！
I can't believe what you did. Monica's gonna kill you.
看，看，看 这个“漂脑袋”作了什么？
Look! Look! Look what the.. Look what the floating heads did!
没关系。
I don't care.
怎么了？
What's going on?
是领养管理处打来的。
That was the adoption agency.
然后？
And?
-我们可以领养孩子了！ -真的么？
- We're getting a baby! - Are you serious?!
有个俄亥俄州的孕妇选了我们！
There's a pregnant woman in Ohio,and she picked us.
-恭喜！真为你们高兴！ - 太好了！
- Oh,my God,that's great! - That's incredible.
恭喜你们！
I'm so happy for you.
今年的感恩节比去年好太多了！
This Thanksgiving kicks last Thanksgiving's ass!
敬莫尼卡和钱德 还有那俄亥俄州的小家伙！
To Monica and Chandler and that knocked-up girl in Ohio.
你们两个终于有孩子了，这真让我高兴。
I'm just so happy you guys are finally getting a kid.
你们没考虑过怀孕么？
I know. Have you considered pageanting?
他们打来电话，我们就会有孩子了 这真是不可思议！
I can't believe they called. I mean,we're actually getting a baby.
我能体会你们的感受。
I know how you feel.
-真的？ -当然啦
- Really? - Sure.
我以前为了买爱丽舍・梅・艾莫瑞经历过完全相同的事情
I went through the exact same thing with Alicia May Emory.
那种期待，那种迷茫
The waiting,the wondering.
直到有一天 我从玩具反斗城买到了她！
Then one day,I get that call from Toys "R" Us.
她又有货了！
She was in stock.
确实“完全相同”。
That is the exact same thing.